
    <rss version="2.0">
      <channel>
        <title>TOP 8 PLANTS</title>
        <description> DESCRIPTION: Aici găsiți clasamentul celor mai populare plante colectate.</description>
        <language> Language:  en</language>
        <lastBuildDate> DOWNLOAD NOW : Tue Jun 27 2023 18:17:50 GMT+0300 (Eastern European Summer Time)</lastBuildDate>
        
        <item>
          <name>NAME: orchid</name>
          <top>NR. OF APPEARANCES: 4 </top>
          <category>CATEGORY: house</category>
          <type>TYPE: flower </type>
          <season>SEASON: spring </season>
          <color>COLOR: pink</color>      
          <description>DESCRIPTION: Orchids are a diverse and widespread family of flowering plants, with blooms that are often colourful and fragrant. The definition of orchid is a flowering plant of the orchid family, which is the biggest family of flowering plants in the world.</description>
          <language>LANGUAGE: EN</language>
          <pubDate>PUBLIC DATE: Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:17:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
      
        <item>
          <name>NAME: peace lily</name>
          <top>NR. OF APPEARANCES: 3 </top>
          <category>CATEGORY: house</category>
          <type>TYPE: flower </type>
          <season>SEASON: summer </season>
          <color>COLOR: white</color>      
          <description>DESCRIPTION: Peace lilies are tropical, evergreen plants that thrive on the forest floor, where they receive dappled sunlight and consistent moisture. Replicating these conditions in the home is the key to getting your peace lily to be happy, healthy, and thriving.</description>
          <language>LANGUAGE: EN</language>
          <pubDate>PUBLIC DATE: Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:17:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
      
        <item>
          <name>NAME: dandelion</name>
          <top>NR. OF APPEARANCES: 2 </top>
          <category>CATEGORY: medicinal</category>
          <type>TYPE: herb </type>
          <season>SEASON: spring </season>
          <color>COLOR: yellow</color>      
          <description>DESCRIPTION: Taraxacum is a large genus of flowering plants in the family Asteraceae, which consists of species commonly known as dandelions. They are native to Eurasia and North America, but the two commonplace species worldwide, T. officinale and T. erythrospermum, were imports from Europe that now propagate as wildflowers.</description>
          <language>LANGUAGE: EN</language>
          <pubDate>PUBLIC DATE: Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:17:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
      
        <item>
          <name>NAME: salvia</name>
          <top>NR. OF APPEARANCES: 2 </top>
          <category>CATEGORY: medicinal</category>
          <type>TYPE: shrub </type>
          <season>SEASON: all </season>
          <color>COLOR: purple</color>      
          <description>DESCRIPTION: Salvia is the largest genus of plants in the mint family, Lamiaceae, with nearly 1000 species of shrubs, herbaceous perennials, and annuals. Within the Lamiaceae, Salvia is part of the tribe Mentheae within the subfamily Nepetoideae.</description>
          <language>LANGUAGE: EN</language>
          <pubDate>PUBLIC DATE: Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:17:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
      
        <item>
          <name>NAME: violet</name>
          <top>NR. OF APPEARANCES: 2 </top>
          <category>CATEGORY: garden</category>
          <type>TYPE: flower </type>
          <season>SEASON: spring </season>
          <color>COLOR: purple</color>      
          <description>DESCRIPTION: Violets are a genus of flowering plants in the family Violaceae. It is the largest genus in the family, containing between 525 and 600 species.</description>
          <language>LANGUAGE: EN</language>
          <pubDate>PUBLIC DATE: Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:17:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
      
        <item>
          <name>NAME: dahlias</name>
          <top>NR. OF APPEARANCES: 2 </top>
          <category>CATEGORY: garden</category>
          <type>TYPE: flower </type>
          <season>SEASON: summer </season>
          <color>COLOR: purple</color>      
          <description>DESCRIPTION: Dahlias are a genus of bushy, tuberous, herbaceous perennial plants native to Mexico and Central America. A member of the Asteraceae, dicotyledonous plants, related species include the sunflower, daisy, chrysanthemum, and zinnia.</description>
          <language>LANGUAGE: EN</language>
          <pubDate>PUBLIC DATE: Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:17:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
      
        <item>
          <name>NAME: roses</name>
          <top>NR. OF APPEARANCES: 2 </top>
          <category>CATEGORY: garden</category>
          <type>TYPE: flower </type>
          <season>SEASON: summer </season>
          <color>COLOR: red</color>      
          <description>DESCRIPTION: Roses are a popular crop for both domestic and commercial cut flowers. Generally they are harvested and cut when in bud, and held in refrigerated conditions until ready for display at their point of sale.</description>
          <language>LANGUAGE: EN</language>
          <pubDate>PUBLIC DATE: Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:17:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
      
        <item>
          <name>NAME: ameryllis</name>
          <top>NR. OF APPEARANCES: 2 </top>
          <category>CATEGORY: house</category>
          <type>TYPE: flower </type>
          <season>SEASON: winter </season>
          <color>COLOR: red</color>      
          <description>DESCRIPTION: Amaryllis is a genus of flowering plants that are native to South Africa and South America. They are known for their large, showy flowers that bloom in a variety of colors, including red, pink, white, and orange. Amaryllis plants are popular as houseplants and are often given as gifts during the winter holiday season.</description>
          <language>LANGUAGE: EN</language>
          <pubDate>PUBLIC DATE: Tue, 27 Jun 2023 15:17:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
      
      </channel>
    </rss>
  